<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrollview</string>
    <string name="royal_university_of_bhutan">Royal University of Bhutan.</string>
    <string name="information">The Royal University of Bhutan was launched on 2nd June 2003 to provide tertiary education in Bhutan. The Royal Charter and the Statutes provide the legal instruments for the University.

The overall rationale of the University as set out in the Royal Charter and Statutes is the "dissemination of knowledge and the advancement of learning through a balanced, well regulated and sound tertiary education system for the economic and cultural development of the Kingdom of Bhutan and to promote the cultural enrichment, personal development and well being of our people."

The specific objectives of the University are:

    to develope and provide programmes of study at tertiary education level, of relevance and good quality which will fulfill the needs of the country for an educated and skilled population, and
    to promote and conduct research, to contribute to the creation of knowledge in an international context and to promote the transfer of knowledge of relevance to Bhutan.

(Royal Charter and the Statutes of the Royal University of Bhutan 2003:3)

RUB Vision, Mission and Core Values
VISION

An internationally recognized university steeped in GNH values
MISSION

    To provide programmes of study at tertiary education level, of relevance and good quality which will fulfill the needs of the country for an educated, skilled and humane population;
    To promote and conduct research to contribute to the creation of knowledge of relevance to Bhutan, and
    To provide training and professional services for the enhancement of knowledge, capacity building and community development.

CORE VALUES

    Love for learning
    Compassion and fairness
    Creativity and innovation
    Community services
    Accountability
    Responsibility
    Professionalism
    Respect for diversity of views
    Respect for the environment
</string>
</resources>